comicartcommunity.com 2007-06-09

# Comic Art Community AUCTIONS Original Comic Book Art, Chat and Gallery

**User Agreement**  
 **Rules For Sellers**  
 **Waiver Of Liability**  
 **Terms Of Use**  
 **Prohibited Items**  
 **Legal Notice for Copyright Holders**  
 **Advertise On This Site!**  
 **How To Make A Shorter URL**  
 **Rules For Buyers**  
 **Tax Policy**  
| Privacy Policy  

**Privacy Policy**

The privacy practices of this statement apply to our services available under the domain and sub-domains of www.dragonberry.com.com and apply generally to our subsidiaries or joint venture Web sites. 

By visiting these Web sites you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. _If you do not agree please do not use or access our services._

As described below, as part of the normal operation of our services, your information is collected by us, disclosed to third parties and used by third parties and us. 

This Privacy Policy describes the information we collect about you and what may happen to that information. All of our subsidiaries and joint ventures operate under similar privacy practices as described in this Privacy Policy and, subject to the requirements of applicable law, we strive to provide a consistent set of privacy practices throughout the trading community. 

By accepting the Privacy Policy and the User Agreement in registration, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms of the User Agreement. 

This Privacy Policy is effective on March 8th, 2003 forward for all users. 

**1\. A special note about children**

_Children are not eligible to use our services and we ask that minors (under the age of 18) do not submit any personal information to us_. 

**2\. Information we collect**

Our primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you with a smooth, efficient, and customized experience. This allows us to provide services and features that most likely meet your needs, and to customize our service to make your experience easier. 

In general, you can browse our site without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. Once you give us your personal information, you are not anonymous to us. If you choose to use our services, we may require you to provide: 

contact and identity information 

billing information 

shipping information , and 

other personal information as indicated on the forms throughout our site. 

Where possible, we indicate which information is required and which information is optional. 

You always have the option to not provide information by choosing not to use a particular service or feature. 

Under some circumstances we may require some additional financial information, such as, but not limited to: 

if you are registering using an email account at a free email service, or 

registering to sell on our site. 

We may use your financial information, including credit card information to verify your name, address, and other information, as well as to bill you for your use of our services. 

We automatically track certain information based upon your behavior on our site. We use this information to do internal research on our users' demographics, interests, and behavior to better understand and serve you and our community. This information may include: 

the Web address that you just came from (whether this Web address is on our site or not) 

the Web address you next go to (whether this Web address is on our site or not) 

the browser you are using, and 

the IP address of your computer. 

We use data collection devices such as "cookies" on certain pages of our site to help analyze our Web page flow, measure promotional effectiveness, and promote trust and safety. 

Cookies are small files placed on your hard drive that assist us in providing customized services. We offer certain features that are only available through the use of a cookie. We also use cookies to allow you to enter your password less frequently during a session. Cookies can also help us provide information that is targeted to your interests. 

Most cookies are "session cookies," meaning that they are automatically deleted from your computer at the end of a session. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although in that case you may not be able to use certain features on our site and you may be required to reenter your password more frequently during a session. 

Additionally, you may encounter cookies or other similar devices on certain pages of our site that are placed by third parties. For example, if you view a Web page created by a user, there may be a cookie placed within that Web page. We do not control the use of cookies by third parties. 

Other instances when we collect your information 

If you choose to bid, buy or sell on our site, we collect information about your bidding, buying and selling behavior. 

We also collect other users' comments about you in our feedback area. 

If you establish a credit account with us to pay the fees we charge, we collect some additional information, including a billing address, a credit card number and a credit card expiration date and tracking information from checks or money orders. 

If you choose to post messages in our boards, chat rooms or other message areas or leave feedback for other users, we collect that information you provide to us. 

If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on the site, we may collect such information into a file specific to you. 

If you register on another Web site or use a Web site providing a service for us or a Web site that helps facilitate your activity on our site, that Web site may provide personal information about you and your transactions back to us. 

**3\. Our use of your information**

We use your information to facilitate the services you request. We use information in the file we maintain about you, and other information we obtain from your current and past activities on the site, to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our User Agreement. At times, we may look across multiple users to identify problems or resolve disputes, and in particular we may examine your information to identify users using multiple User IDs or aliases. 

If you choose to list an item for sale on our site or open a credit account, or otherwise provide us with your credit card information, we use your address and billing information to bill you and provide associated support. 

You agree that we may use personally identifiable information about you to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to analyze site usage, improve our content and product offerings, and customize our site's content, layout, and services. These uses improve our site and better tailor it to meet your needs. 

You agree that we may use your information to contact you and deliver information to you that, in some cases, are targeted to your interests, such as targeted banner advertisements, administrative notices, product offerings, and communications relevant to your use of the site. By accepting the User Agreement and Privacy Policy, you expressly agree to receive this information. If you do not wish to receive these communications, we encourage you to choose not to receive certain communications on the notification preferences page. You may make changes to your notification preferences at any time. 

**4\. Our disclosure of your information.**

Due to the existing regulatory environment, we cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. By way of example (without limiting the foregoing), we may be forced to disclose information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, or users may abuse or misuse your information that they collect from our site. Therefore, although we use industry standard practices to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personally identifiable information or private communications will always remain private. 

Community 

Throughout the site, you are identified by your User ID. If you select your email address as your User ID you will disclose your email address to other users and third parties. As a result, other users and third parties might send you unsolicited email and be able to personally identify all of your public activities on the site. Although our pages are coded with robot exclusion headers, others may illegally attempt to automatically collect your email address from our site. We describe how to change your User ID below. Even if your User ID is not your email address, your User ID can be used to identify you and your activities throughout the site. Other people can see your bids, items that you have purchased in the past, your feedback rating and associated comments, your postings on the site, and so on. 

We also provide a number of ways to allow other users to find out more about you and your site activities, such as our feature that allows users to quickly see all of the items you are offering at the time. If you are involved in a transaction, we have a feature that allows other users to view your email address and obtain your contact information. Further, we may send out notices to other community members regarding your actions on our site. 

External service providers 

There are a number of services offered by external service providers that help you use our site (for example, co-branded sites, listing agents, escrow, authentication, mediation). If you choose to use these optional services, disclose information to the external service providers, and/or grant them permission to collect information about you, then their use of your information is governed by their privacy policy. 

We may, for your convenience, provide some of your personally identifiable information to the external service provider offering such services. However, before we disclose your personally identifiable information to an external service provider, you will see what data is about to be sent and have the ability to approve the disclosure. To prevent our disclosure of your personally identifiable information to an external service provider, you can decline such disclosures or simply not use their services. Because we do not control the privacy practices of these third parties, you should evaluate their practices before deciding to use their services. 

Users who register on a co-branded web site (for example, CompuServe, AOL.com, and AOL) grant eBay permission to pass your email address back to that co-branded web site and affiliated Web sites. The use of such information by the co-branded and affiliated Web sites is limited by their applicable privacy policies. 

Internal service providers 

We may use internal service providers to facilitate our services (for example, search, discussion boards, surveys) and therefore we may provide some of your personally identifiable information directly to them. In some instances, the internal service provider may collect information directly from you (such as the situation where we ask a internal service provider to conduct a survey for us). In these cases, you will be notified of the involvement of the internal service provider, and all information disclosures you make will be strictly optional .

In all cases, these internal service providers' use of information we supply them is restricted by confidentiality agreements. If you provide additional information to an internal service provider directly, then their use of your information is governed by their applicable privacy policy. 

Other corporate entities 

We share much of our data, including personally identifiable information about you, with our subsidiaries and joint ventures that are committed to serving your online trading needs and related services, throughout the world. To the extent that these entities have access to your information, they will treat it at least as protectively as they treat information they obtain from their other users. Our subsidiaries and joint ventures follow privacy practices no less protective of all users than our practices described in this document, to the extent allowed by applicable law. It is possible that us, our subsidiaries, our joint ventures, or any combination of such, could merge with or be acquired by another business entity. Should such a combination occur, you should expect that we would share some or all of your information in order to continue to provide the service. 

Legal requests 

We cooperate with law enforcement inquiries, as well as other third parties to enforce laws, such as: intellectual property rights, fraud and other rights. We can (and you authorize us to) disclose any information about you to law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate, in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, or other activity that is illegal or may expose us or you to legal liability. 

Further, we can (and you authorize us to) disclose your User ID, name, street address, city, state, zip code, country, phone number, email, and company name to Rights Owner (RO) program participants as we in our sole discretion believe necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement, piracy, or other unlawful activity. 

Additionally, we reserve the right (and you authorize us) to communicate any information about you (including, but not limited to your policy violations, ended items, and item status) to other users, law enforcement and RO members as we in our sole discretion determine necessary or appropriate to maintain a level of trust and safety in our community and to enforce our User Agreement, Privacy Policy and any posted policies or rules applicable to services you use through our site. 

**5\. Your use of other users' information**

In order to facilitate interaction among all community members, our service allows you limited access other users' contact information. As a seller you have access to the User ID, email address and other contact information of the buyer or winning bidder(s), and as a buyer or winning bidder you have access to the User ID, email address and other contact information of the seller. 

By entering into our User Agreement, you agree that, with respect to other users' personally identifiable information that you obtain through the site or through a communication or facilitated transaction, we hereby grant to you a license to use such information only for: 

Auction-related communications that are not unsolicited commercial messages 

using services offered through us (for example, escrow, insurance, shipping and fraud complaints), and 

any other purpose that such user expressly agrees to after adequate disclosure of the purpose(s). 

In all cases, you must give users an opportunity to remove themselves from your database and a chance to review what information you have collected about them. In addition, under no circumstances, except as defined in this section, can you disclose personally identifiable information about another user to any third party without our consent and the consent of such other user after adequate disclosure. Note that law enforcement personnel, RO program participants, and other rights holders are given different rights with respect to information they access. 

**We and our users do not tolerate unsolicited email (spam)**. Therefore, without limiting the foregoing, you are not licensed to add an eBay user, even a user who has purchased an item from you, to your mail list (email or physical mail) without their express consent after adequate disclosure. 

**6\. Use of email tools**

You may not use the "Email This Auction to a Friend" service or other email forwarding services that we offer to send spam or otherwise send content that would violate our User Agreement. We do not permanently store the email messages or the email addresses. 

If you send and email using the "Email This Auction to a Friend" service to an email address that is not registered in our community, we do not use that email address for any purpose other than to send your email. We do not rent or sell these email addresses. We generally discard the email addresses some time after they have been used to send your email. 

**7\. Control of your password**

You are responsible for all actions taken with your User ID and password, including fees. Therefore we do not recommend that you disclose your eBay password to any third parties. If you choose to share your User ID and password or your information with third parties to provide you additional services, you are responsible for all actions taken with your User ID and password and therefore you should review that third party's privacy policy. 

If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personally identifiable information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately change your password .

**8\. Reviewing and changing your personally identifiable information.**

We offer you the ability to automatically review and change the information you submit to us by logging into the site and entering in the new information yourself. Generally, we will not modify your information based on your request because it is very difficult to authenticate your account manually. You can change your User ID, email address, contact information, financial information, shipping information and user preferences by going to the preferences and setup section in your profile . You must promptly update your information if it changes. Once posted, you may not be able to change or remove any public postings made on our site including our chat rooms or other message areas or the feedback area. 

Upon your request, we will deactivate your User ID, contact information, billing information, shipping information, and financial information from our active databases to prevent your information from being shared with other users. To make this request, please email privacy@dragonberry.com . Such information will be deactivated as soon as reasonably possible based on your User ID activity and in accordance with our deactivation policy and applicable law. 

We will retain in our files information you have requested to remove in some circumstances, such as to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our User Agreement. Further, such prior information is never completely removed from our databases due to technical and legal constraints, including stored "back up" systems. Therefore, you should not expect that all of your personally identifiable information will be completely removed from our databases in response to your requests. 

**9\. Other information collectors**

Except as otherwise expressly included in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. To the extent that you disclose your information to other parties, whether they are bidders, buyers or sellers on our site or other sites throughout the Internet, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you disclose to them. To the extent that we use third party advertisers, they adhere to their own privacy policies. Since we do not control the privacy policies of third parties, you are subject to the privacy policies of that third party. We encourage you to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others .

**10\. Security**

We use industry few standard practices to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal identifiable information. However, "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet. 

**11\. Conflict of terms**

It is our goal to make our privacy practices easy to understand. We have created easy-to-read summaries, privacy principles, a privacy chart and, are working on privacy enhancing technology to help summarize our full privacy policy. If you have questions about any part of this summary or if you would like more detailed information, we encourage you to review our full privacy policy. 

**12\. Notice**

We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the amended terms on our site.

If you have additional privacy related questions, you may send email to [privacy@dragonberry.com](mailto:privacy@dragonberry.com) .
